This is TubeWatch.
It answers one question: what should your next video be?
Connect your channel and it's already working — it auto-tracks competitors your size,
in your niche, and pulls in their breakouts.
These scores aren't view counts — that's how many times faster a video is growing than its own channel's normal.
The Breakouts feed is the whole game.
Every video here is overperforming its channel right now — filter by niche, by multiplier, or search a topic.
Found one worth copying? Ask the AI why it broke out.
It compares the video against that channel's own baseline — the title angle, the length, the hook —
and tells you whether to copy the topic fast, or steal the format forever.
That's TubeWatch. Free to start — link below.